export const data = [
    {
      question: "Who is making the web standards?",
        option1: "Mozilla",
         option2: "Microsoft",
         option3: "The World Wide Web Consortium",
         option4: "Google",
         ans:3,
    },
    {
      question: "How can you open a link in a new browser window?",
      
         option1: "Target", 
         option2: "_blank", 
         option3: "Same", 
         option4: "Open", 
         ans:2
    
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define a hyperlink in HTML?",
   
           option1: "<a>", 
           option2: "<link>", 
           option3: "<href>", 
           option4: "<url>", 
          ans:1
        
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to specify the image source in HTML?",
    
           option1: "<a>",
           option2: "<link>", 
           option3: "<href>", 
           option4: "<url>", 
          ans:1
        
    },
    {
      question: "What does the <title> tag define in an HTML document?",
     
           option1: "The title displayed inside the document", 
           option2: "The heading of the body", 
           option3: "The title displayed in the browser tab", 
           option4: "The background color of the page", 
          ans:3
      
    },
    {
      question: "Which CSS property is used to add space between the text and its container?",
    
           option1: "border", 
           option2: "margin", 
           option3: "spacing", 
          option4: "padding",
          ans:4

    },
    {
      question: "How do you select an element with the class name example in CSS?",
      
           option1: "#example", 
           option2: ".example", 
           option3: "spacing", 
           option4: "padding", 
          ans:2
     
    },
    {
      question: "What is the default display value for an HTML <div> element?",
    
           option1: "inline-block",
           option2: "inline", 
           option3: "block",
           option4: "none", 
          ans:3
       
    },
    {
      question: "How do you center an element horizontally in CSS?",
   
           option1: "text-align: center;",
           option2: "align-items: center;",
           option3: "justify-content: center;",
          option4: "margin: 0 auto", 
           ans:4
     
    },
    {
      question: "What is the default value of the position property in CSS?",
     
           option1: "absolute", 
           option2: "static",
           option3: "fixed", 
           option4: "relative",
          ans:2
        
    },
    {
      question: "Which JavaScript function is used to display an alert box with a message?",
   
          option1: "alert()",
           option2: "msg()", 
           option3: "log()",
          option4: "print()",
          ans:1
       
    },
    {
      question: "Which operator is used to compare both value and type in JavaScript",

           option1: "==", 
           option2: "!=", 
           option3: "===", 
           option4: "!==",
          ans:3
      
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the correct way to declare a JavaScript variable?",
           option1: "let 10 = x", 
           option2: "variable x = 10", 
           option3: "int x = 10;", 
           option4: "var x = 10;", 
          ans:4
    
    },
    {
      question: "Which method is used to round a number to the nearest integer in JavaScript?",
 
           option1: "Math.ceil()", 
           option2: "Math.floor()", 
           option3: "Math.random()", 
          option4: "Math.round()", 
          ans:4
    
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is used to define a function in JavaScript?",
         option1: "function myFunction() { }",
           option2: "def myFunction() { }", 
           option3: "func myFunction() { }",
           option4: "create function myFunction() { }",
          ans:1
    
    }
  
  
  ];